<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-05-27T16:15:01-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Andrew Choi</title><subtitle>Personal blog!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Remote work: dislocation or secular shift?</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2020/05/27/remote-work-dislocation-or-secular-shift.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Remote work: dislocation or secular shift?" /><published>2020-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2020-05-27T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2020/05/27/remote-work-dislocation-or-secular-shift</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2020/05/27/remote-work-dislocation-or-secular-shift.html">&lt;p&gt;There seems to be a divide in coronavirus trend coverage around the topic about a shift to remote work.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There were two metacognitive points from a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cZmRtQCR2ns&quot;&gt;recent conversation with Larry Summers&lt;/a&gt; that resonated with me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The first was that most trends are not necessarily being reversed by the crisis. Some trends are being accelerated (exodus of second and beyond firms from high-cost areas) and some have been halted (sharing economy a la Uber/Airbnb). That being said, the crisis itself is not enough of a justification for changing the overall arc of the macro trend–absent changing macro incentives and conditions, the trend is likely to revert to the pre-crisis behavior once the crisis passes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second was that most people adhere to a “more now than ever” behavior when considering the impact of a crisis on concerns that they’ve already had.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One trend that seems to be getting a lot of play is that now that COVID-19 has made many more workers remote than would be otherwise, managers are seeing the benefits of remote-first workplaces. I think this is erroneous for a few reasons:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Often, people point to the fact that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/jackkelly/2020/05/13/twitter-ceo-jack-dorsey-tells-employees-they-can-work-from-home-forever-before-you-celebrate-theres-a-catch/&quot;&gt;executives at a number of leading firms have decided to extend remote working policies&lt;/a&gt;, and often in quite unexpected ways. I think this is not necessarily indicative of successful pivoting for these organizations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The crucial issue is that in many of these orgs, the majority of people report to middle managers, not to the top level exec. While execs (and maybe even the top tier of middle managers) may believe wholeheartedly in this step, I suspect there is a modal group of middle managers who do not yet have the requisite skills to be successful remote managers. Additionally, in that group, there are likely a number managers that rely on intuition-based indicators of success (such as face time, presence, and other unconscious biases) that will be lost in how to translate those into a remote situation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we’re in a state of exploiting the culture that has been developed in-person for existing orgs. As team members turn over, continuity of team and org culture will be even more difficult to extend to new team members in a remote-first scenario.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the crisis has led to a wide reevaluation of in-person-first teams, I suspect the dislocation of workers from physical workspaces is temporary, and once a vaccine is widely available, workplace cultures and expectations around presence will mostly revert.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">There seems to be a divide in coronavirus trend coverage around the topic about a shift to remote work.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Fixing Spotify Desktop on HiDPI displays on Ubuntu 19.04</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/09/09/spotify-desktop-snap-for-hidpi-ubuntu.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Fixing Spotify Desktop on HiDPI displays on Ubuntu 19.04" /><published>2019-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</published><updated>2019-09-09T00:00:00-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/09/09/spotify-desktop-snap-for-hidpi-ubuntu</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/09/09/spotify-desktop-snap-for-hidpi-ubuntu.html">&lt;p&gt;With the new version of Spotify delivered via &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;snap&lt;/code&gt;, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://community.spotify.com/t5/Desktop-Linux/Linux-client-barely-usable-on-HiDPI-displays/td-p/1067272&quot;&gt;original fix&lt;/a&gt; references a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;.desktop&lt;/code&gt; file that no longer exists. The new desktop file can be found at:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/lib/snapd/desktop/applications/spotify_spotify.desktop&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adding the requisite &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;--force-device-scale-factor=2&lt;/code&gt; before the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;%U&lt;/code&gt; in the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Exec&lt;/code&gt; line fixes the desktop client being too small to read!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">With the new version of Spotify delivered via snap, the original fix references a .desktop file that no longer exists. The new desktop file can be found at:</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Dealing with ACPI wakeups</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/01/02/acpi-debugging.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Dealing with ACPI wakeups" /><published>2019-01-02T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-01-02T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/01/02/acpi-debugging</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2019/01/02/acpi-debugging.html">&lt;p&gt;I’ve been having an issue with my laptop waking up from sleep after I’ve closed the lid to send it into suspend. This would drain battery and overheat the laptop, especially when placed into a backpack or bag! Very frustrating to get to wherever you’re going and realize that your laptop is dead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a Macbook Pro from 2015, and it’s running Ubuntu 18.10.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After investigating what was happening via &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/log/syslog&lt;/code&gt; examination, I found a number of errors happening due to ARP table lookups. I spent a while trying to fix that, but eventually settled on a solution that just disabled wake-over-WiFi.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I checked what was able to wake up the device with:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;cat /proc/acpi/wakeup&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Which displayed a table that looked like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;Device	S-state	  Status   Sysfs node
PEG0	  S3	*disabled  pci:0000:00:01.0
PEG1	  S3	*disabled  pci:0000:00:01.1
PEG2	  S3	*disabled
ARPT	  S4	*enabled   pci:0000:03:00.0
RP04	  S3	*disabled  pci:0000:00:1c.3
XHC1	  S3	*enabled   pci:0000:00:14.0
ADP1	  S4	*disabled  platform:ACPI0003:00
LID0	  S4	*enabled   platform:PNP0C0D:00
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After some digging in &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/var/log/syslog&lt;/code&gt;, I found out that there were a number of wakeups happening because of ARP table issues. I had a hunch that the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ARPT&lt;/code&gt; device was linked to that, and disabled it by creating a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;/etc/rc.local&lt;/code&gt; file. This file runs every time the computer boots, and mine looks like this:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;c&quot;&gt;#! /bin/sh&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;nb&quot;&gt;echo &lt;/span&gt;ARPT &lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;&amp;gt;&lt;/span&gt; /proc/acpi/wakeup
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Don’t forget to make it executable via a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;chmod +x /etc/rc.local&lt;/code&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">I’ve been having an issue with my laptop waking up from sleep after I’ve closed the lid to send it into suspend. This would drain battery and overheat the laptop, especially when placed into a backpack or bag! Very frustrating to get to wherever you’re going and realize that your laptop is dead.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Where are the pop-ups in a box?</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/11/27/pop-up-in-a-box.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Where are the pop-ups in a box?" /><published>2018-11-27T10:23:45-05:00</published><updated>2018-11-27T10:23:45-05:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/11/27/pop-up-in-a-box</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/11/27/pop-up-in-a-box.html">&lt;p&gt;A combination of trends in the branding world have converged such that there is an opportunity for a “pop-up experience in a box” company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer goods startups, many of whom are direct-to-consumer, are really driving most of the growth in the overall consumer goods world. According to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.forbes.com/sites/andriacheng/2018/07/10/changing-consumer-behavior-has-pushed-cpg-giants-buying-binge-to-a-15-year-high/#2f37b6364944&quot;&gt;Forbes and OC&amp;amp;C Strategy Consultants’ annual Global 50 report&lt;/a&gt; in 2018, there were 60 M&amp;amp;A transactions from the world’s top 50 consumer goods companies, “the total value of [which] nearly tripled to $145 billion last year from 2016.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consumer goods startups are highly valued. How are they reaching their customers and establishing themselves as brands?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One factor seems to be a groundswell of social media, especially visually. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.recode.net/2018/10/9/17938356/facebook-instagram-future-revenue-growth-kevin-systrom&quot;&gt;According to Andy Hargreaves&lt;/a&gt;, a research analyst with KeyBanc Capital Markets, Instagram is expected to grow “to about 30 percent of Facebook’s ad revenue in two years, as well as nearly 70 percent of the company’s new revenue by 2020.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As an observer on the ground in NYC, it seems that pop-up culture is taking over. A friend and I walked into a cosmetics store to find a new kind of lip balm (which, incidentally, she told me she had seen on Instagram) and we were almost immediately pitched the pop-up cosmetic “experience” in the rear of the store. As a cherry on top, it seems that a number of these pop-up locations are actually charging for admission–a brilliant move to kill two birds with one stone.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This trend is nothing new for many: from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theverge.com/2017/7/20/16000552/instagram-restaurant-interior-design-photo-friendly-media-noche&quot;&gt;restaurants designed from the ground up to appeal to the phone camera&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.eater.com/2017/7/6/15925940/instagram-influencers-cronuts-milkshakes-burgers&quot;&gt;changing the actual kinds of food we buy (and not necessarily eat)&lt;/a&gt;, the culture is pervasive. For some, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.theinfatuation.com/new-york/reviews/while-we-were-young&quot;&gt;counterculture&lt;/a&gt; is already here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If Instagram is driving much of influencer and consumption culture, and there is an opportunity for brands to mobilize every visitor to their stores as an ambassador for their brand, why aren’t more brands taking advantage?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chief risk in running a pop-up experience seems to be that most of these organizations are internet-first operations, running either direct-to-consumer or without a physical presence. There are, however, many brands and organizations that have meaningful experience with these experiences. It seems to me that there must be a pattern behind what makes something successful (e.g. well-lit, good camera angles, static displays, sufficient space to avoid overcrowding, etc.) and that these patterns can be leveraged into a company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Whether this company takes the form of a consultancy or something closer to a “pop-up experience in a box” product, I don’t know. But I feel confident that as more brands work to foster an image and goodwill within the influencer and consumer space, somebody will start to act as a guide.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The opportunities seem even greater when you consider the fact that retail spaces and malls across the country have suffered lower occupancy rates and difficulty leasing, and that many of these spaces are located in non-metropolitan areas. For the portion of the country that is not in a position to stumble into a brand-friendly Instagram situation, helping them along may provide a boost in the long tail of consumers across the nation.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A combination of trends in the branding world have converged such that there is an opportunity for a “pop-up experience in a box” company.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">A Few Thoughts re: “Technological Trends, Financial Capital, and the Dynamics of Disruption”</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/09/25/a16z-trends-capital-disruption.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="A Few Thoughts re: “Technological Trends, Financial Capital, and the Dynamics of Disruption”" /><published>2018-09-25T23:17:07-04:00</published><updated>2018-09-25T23:17:07-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/09/25/a16z-trends-capital-disruption</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2018/09/25/a16z-trends-capital-disruption.html">&lt;p&gt;a16z podcast &lt;a href=&quot;https://a16z.com/2018/09/23/tech-trends-disruption-innovation-internet-crypto/&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few thoughts on the above-mentioned podcast:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;scarcity-digitalcrypto-goods-vs-drm&quot;&gt;Scarcity: digital/crypto goods vs DRM&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The entire time that Chris Dixon talks about the idea of crypto goods (to borrow the a16z term) enabling scarcity in digital environments, I was waiting for a mention of DRM. Aside from a brief mention that gets talked over by Wilson, there seems to be no serious discussion about the difference between the digital goods model vs. more traditional prior attempts at DRM. There’s a snippet where Wilson talks about replicability being the reason why a number of digital business models have failed, but it seems to me that DRM was previously touted as that solution in the past.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To me, the nuance is that the central question is not of ownership, but of consumption–even if the crypto space provides an unambiguous record of who owns a specific song, what prevents other people from enjoying that song? The value for the consumer of a piece of music or art or movie is not that I have title to the work (because in some real sense I do not–the actual piece of music or movie is generally owned by a third party!) but whether or not I have the ability to enjoy it on demand. What is the value of digital goods (if not in resale) otherwise?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;traditional-economist-objection-to-cryptocurrencies&quot;&gt;“Traditional” economist objection to cryptocurrencies&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wilson and Dixon make the simplifying assumption that there are a large number of traditional economists who have written off the fundamental value of bitcoin and other cryptocurrencies because “at the end of the day, they’re just electronic bytes”. This serves as a catalyst for a great discussion about the primacy of commerce vs. e-commerce, sports vs. e-sports, which resonated with me. However, the view that I hold wrt the fundamental value of cryptocurrencies is that there is no physical power that has a vested interest in the continuation of the monetary fiction. To paraphrase, how many legions has Bitcoin?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;digital-natives&quot;&gt;Digital natives&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another point that gets made is that the innovation in digital goods is spreading faster in the gaming arena than in other areas. There’s also another interesting corollary here, which is that there were a number of communities that have adopted these goods before even US gamers have (wrt Fornite et al). Line, lest we forget, became a contender in the messaging space due to a domination of Japanese online communication, and the reason why it was throwing off so much cash was due to online stickers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This would seem to be a point in favor of the thesis that we’re converging recently on a normalization of the digital goods paradigm for the digital natives. The question that one then asks is if we believe that either a) the older generations will adapt to that mental model, or b) if the demographic shift will be rapid enough for these models to become the most important modality of consumption.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a question of adoption, I suspect that (at least) millennials will be resistant to this idea of living as digital-first and digital-only. There’s already a tremendous industry focused on wellness, and it’s mature enough that we see features from major industry players (Apple in iOS, Google in Android) to help focus on things like screen time and (one suspects) to help minimize it.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">a16z podcast here.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">ImportError: undefined symbol: PyUnicodeUCS4_AsUnicodeEscapeString</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2015/03/23/importerror-undefined-symbol-pyunicodeucs4_asunicodeescapestring.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="ImportError: undefined symbol: PyUnicodeUCS4_AsUnicodeEscapeString" /><published>2015-03-23T13:45:16-04:00</published><updated>2015-03-23T13:45:16-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2015/03/23/importerror-undefined-symbol-pyunicodeucs4_asunicodeescapestring</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2015/03/23/importerror-undefined-symbol-pyunicodeucs4_asunicodeescapestring.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;ImportError: ...lib/python2.7/site-packages/numpy/core/multiarray.so: undefined symbol: PyUnicodeUCS4_AsUnicodeEscapeString&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above error means that you've got a Python interpreter compiled against UCS2 trying to run code that was compiled against UCS4. The solution I found was to recompile your lib (here NumPy) using a Python binary compiled with a &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;--enable-unicode=ucs2&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">ImportError: ...lib/python2.7/site-packages/numpy/core/multiarray.so: undefined symbol: PyUnicodeUCS4_AsUnicodeEscapeString</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Custom model Managers in Django</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/12/04/custom-model-managers-in-django.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Custom model Managers in Django" /><published>2014-12-04T10:23:45-05:00</published><updated>2014-12-04T10:23:45-05:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/12/04/custom-model-managers-in-django</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/12/04/custom-model-managers-in-django.html">&lt;p&gt;Be aware: if you’re trying to use a custom model manager in Django, any inclusion of a manager will remove the default &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;objects&lt;/code&gt; manager. Be sure to re-include it if you’re just extending your models!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Be aware: if you’re trying to use a custom model manager in Django, any inclusion of a manager will remove the default objects manager. Be sure to re-include it if you’re just extending your models!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Classes with d3 SVGs</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/10/10/classes-with-d3-svgs.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Classes with d3 SVGs" /><published>2014-10-10T13:31:24-04:00</published><updated>2014-10-10T13:31:24-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/10/10/classes-with-d3-svgs</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2014/10/10/classes-with-d3-svgs.html">&lt;p&gt;Today I was working on toggling classes of elements in a d3-generated SVG, and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;addClass&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;removeClass&lt;/code&gt; weren't working. I verified that my selectors were correct, and also surrounded the block with a jQuery document-ready function, but no dice. I switched from using the jQuery &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;addClass&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;removeClass&lt;/code&gt; methods to d3's &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;classed()&lt;/code&gt; function, and the code magically started working!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As a further note, I imagine that the reason why this is the case is that &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;addClass&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;removeClass&lt;/code&gt; don't recognize &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&amp;lt;path&amp;gt;&lt;/code&gt; elements, while the selectors still do.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Today I was working on toggling classes of elements in a d3-generated SVG, and addClass and removeClass weren't working. I verified that my selectors were correct, and also surrounded the block with a jQuery document-ready function, but no dice. I switched from using the jQuery addClass and removeClass methods to d3's classed() function, and the code magically started working!</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">AssertionError in Django templating</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/07/03/assertionerror-no-exception-supplied-in-django-templating.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="AssertionError in Django templating" /><published>2012-07-03T19:35:17-04:00</published><updated>2012-07-03T19:35:17-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/07/03/assertionerror-no-exception-supplied-in-django-templating</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/07/03/assertionerror-no-exception-supplied-in-django-templating.html">&lt;p&gt;Running across this bug is a bit odd, because I wasn’t aware of any assertions that I was making, but this was the offending code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{% if display_type == 'ts' %}
&amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highstock.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
{% else if display_type == 'avg' %}
&amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highcharts.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
{% endif %}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The above code ended up causing an AssertionError: No exception supplied.
The idea was to do a conditional JavaScript import, but the problem actually ended up being in the Django template syntax.  The correction was to replace the “else if” with an “elif”.  Rookie mistake!
Corrected code:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;{% if display_type == 'ts' %}
&amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highstock.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
{% elif display_type == 'avg' %}
&amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highcharts.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt;
&amp;lt;/script&amp;gt;
{% endif %}
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Running across this bug is a bit odd, because I wasn’t aware of any assertions that I was making, but this was the offending code: {% if display_type == 'ts' %} &amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highstock.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; {% else if display_type == 'avg' %} &amp;lt;script src=&quot;/static/highcharts.js&quot; type=&quot;text/javascript&quot;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/script&amp;gt; {% endif %}</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">MySQL WHILE Loops and Different Types of Variables</title><link href="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/06/19/mysql-while-loops-and-different-types-of-variables.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="MySQL WHILE Loops and Different Types of Variables" /><published>2012-06-19T19:21:29-04:00</published><updated>2012-06-19T19:21:29-04:00</updated><id>http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/06/19/mysql-while-loops-and-different-types-of-variables</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://www.andrewychoi.com/writing/2012/06/19/mysql-while-loops-and-different-types-of-variables.html">&lt;p&gt;A few lessons learned today from working with MySQL variables, &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;WHILE&lt;/code&gt; loops, and prepared statements:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;In a continuation statement for the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;WHILE&lt;/code&gt; loop, make sure to use user-defined variables (i.e. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DECLARE foo INT DEFAULT 10&lt;/code&gt; as opposed to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;SET @foo = 10&lt;/code&gt;, which defines a session variable called &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;@foo&lt;/code&gt; to be 10)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;When using these user-defined variables, be sure to &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;DECLARE&lt;/code&gt; them before any other code gets executed. I’m embarrassed to say that this is one of the things that confounded me the most, despite having written more lines in C than in probably any other language.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;More to come as this project continues!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A few lessons learned today from working with MySQL variables, WHILE loops, and prepared statements:</summary></entry></feed>